{
    "subject": "resource/Tania_(artist)",
    "predicate": "ontology/movement",
    "object": "resource/Public_art",
    "human_readable": "Tania's movement is Public art.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9739742279052734,
            "question": "Is Tania involved in public art?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8898441791534424,
            "question": "What makes Tania's work considered 'public art'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8614805340766907,
            "question": "What type of art is Tania's movement?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7505138516426086,
            "question": "What impact might Tania's public art have on viewers?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5710776448249817,
            "question": "How would you describe Tania's artistic expression?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5559820532798767,
            "question": "How does Tania's work interact with the public space?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5398356914520264,
            "question": "How does Tania's work contribute to the understanding of art?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4146702289581299,
            "question": "What are some characteristics of public art?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.32927408814430237,
            "question": "Why is public art important in a community?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.21248076856136322,
            "question": "Can you give an example of a public art installation?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Tania's movement is Public art.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8560_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Why is public art important in a community?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8560_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some characteristics of public art?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8560_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How does Tania's work contribute to the understanding of art?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8560_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8560_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8560_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8560_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8560_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8560_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8560_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8560_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8560_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8560_80.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8560_86.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nLet me know if you have any more queries!  I am still learning, but I am eager to help."
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in JSON format:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents support this triple, as they describe Tania Bruguera's Immigrant Movement International as a long-term art project in the form of an artist-initiated socio-political movement, which can be considered public art."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents support the statement that Tania Bruguera's Immigrant Movement International is a form of public or social art. This can be seen from multiple descriptions in the documents, such as her operating a flexible community space and engaging with various communities and organizations to address political representation and conditions for immigrants."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "Tania Bruguera's Immigrant Movement International is not strictly public art as it primarily functions as a socio-political movement, rather than an artwork intended for the general public. It aims to engage with communities, social service organizations, elected officials, and artists, focusing on immigration reform, rather than being publicly accessible as a piece of art.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}